Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 2 and District 2 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.2
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 2 Locals, 2.
  - Local 237
    - Local 237 Bridgeport Columbia Records, July 26, 1967-October 22, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Local 237 Legislative Committee and Political Action, April 26, 1971-April 10, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Local 237 Leaflet, Statement of UE Local 237 Executive Board Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Local 237 Newspaper Clipping, "CIO Wins Election at Auto Ordnance Plant" (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Local 238
    - Local 238 Finance and Correspondence, June 22, 1978-February 27, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Local 238 Hartford Terry Steam Turbine, May 28, 1937-July 6, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Local 238 East Bridgewater Murry-Carver Company Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, and 710 Forms, June 28, 1978-December 1, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Local 238 (Springfield)
    - Local 238 (Springfield) Officers Lists, November 20, 1946-March 15, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Local 238 (Springfield) Incoming Correspondence, September 23, 1946-July 7, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      - Julius Emspak to James Kupec Regarding Veterans and Finances, September 23, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Kupec Regarding Finances, July 7, 1947; 2.
    - Local 238 (Springfield) Outgoing Correspondence, James Kupec to Julius Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, September 6, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Local 238 (Springfield) Per Capita Report, October 26, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Local 238 (Springfield) Organization, March 7-June 14, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 96)
      - David Bennett to Julius Emspak, March 7, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Bennett, March 20, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Bennett, March 21, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Paul Seymour, March 21, 1945; 4.
      - Herbert Salter to Emspak, June 13, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Salter, June 14, 1945; 6.
    - Local 238 (Springfield) Disbanding, June 4-9, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 97)
      - Jack Davis to Julius Emspak, June 4, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Davis, June 9, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Paul Seymour, June 9, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Davis, June 9, 1947; 4.
  - Local 238 (Boston)
    - Local 238 (Boston) Officers Lists, November 19, 1949-February 21, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - Local 238 (Boston) Incoming Correspondence, December 15, 1949-March 3, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Earl Barbour Regarding Membership Meeting, December 15, 1949; 1.
      - Fitzgerald to WIlliam Wilder Regarding Membership Meeting, March 3, 1950; 2.
    - Local 238 (Boston) Outgoing Correspondence, December 14, 1949-February 27, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Earl Barbour to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting and Inter-union Rivalry, December 14, 1949; 1.
      - William Wilder to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting, February 27, 1950; 2.
    - Local 238 (Boston) Separate Charter, July-December 1949 (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Pat Walsh to Albert Fitzgerald with Petition, July 1949; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Paul Seymour, November 14, 1949; 2.
      - Emspak to Don Tormey, November 30-December 8, 1949; 3-4.
      - Emspak to Earl Barbour, December 8, 1949; 5.
  - Local 239
    - Local 239 Officers Lists, January 13, 1947-February 16, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Local 239 Incoming Correspondence, January 13, 1941-December 19, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - Janet Barish to Edward Wysockie Regarding Finances, November 14, 1946; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to John Alberto Regarding Allis Chalmers Conference and Finances, January 13, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Roger Fosdick, April 28, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Carl Carlson Regarding Allis Chalmers Conference and Finances, November 17-December 1, 1941; 4-5.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Joseph Smith Regarding Finances, July 28, 1942; 6.
      - Emspak to Smith Regarding FInances, November 3-September 29, 1943; 7-8.
      - Emspak to Wysockie Regarding Veterans and Finances, May 7, 1945; 9.
      - Emspak to Smith Regarding Finances, January 31, 1946; 10.
      - Emspak to Helen Slowbogan Regarding Local 239 Allis Chalmers Strike, May 24, 1946; 11.
      - Emspak to Wyscokie Regarding Finances, August 1, 1946; 12.
      - Emspak to Slowbogan Regarding Local 239 Allis Chalmers Strike, August 26-December 19, 1946; 13-25.
    - Local 239 Incoming Correspondence, May 9, 1941-December 31, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 104)
      - Julius Emspak to Edward Ventola Regarding National Strike Fund, December 16, 1952; 1.
      - James Matles to Carl Carlson, May 9, 1941; 2.
      - Matles to Carlson Regarding Local 613 National Defense Mediation Board with May 9, 1941, Local 613 Allis Chalmers Agreement, May 14, 1941; 3.
      - Matles' Secretary to Carlson, November 18, 1941; 4.
      - Matles to Carlson Regarding Wages and Allis Chalmers Conference, November 25, 1941; 5.
      - Matles to Charles Wojchowski Regarding Local 239 Annual Banquet, December 31, 1953; 6.
      - Russ Nixon to Helen Slowbagen Regarding Political Action Committee, October 2, 1947; 7.
      - Nixon to Edward Wysocki Regarding Political Action Committee, November 12, 1947; 8.
    - Local 239 Outgoing Correspondence, January 3, 1941-December 21, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 105)
      - John Alberto to Julius Emspak Regarding Allis Chalmers Conference and Finances, January 3, 1941; 1.
      - Carl Carlson to Emspak Regarding Local 239 Allis Chalmers Collective Bargaining, May 6, 1941; 2.
      - Carlson to Emspak Regarding Allis Chalmers Conference, Finances and Congress of Industrial Organizations, November 14, 1941; 3.
      - Carlson to James Matles Regarding Wages, November 17, 1941; 4.
      - Herbert Charette to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 19, 1943; 5.
      - Roger Fosdick to Emspak Regarding Local 239 Allis Chalmers Collective Bargaining with April 14, 1941, R. Bechtner Letter to Carlson, April 19, 1941; 6.
      - Joseph Smith to Emspak Regarding Local 239 Allis Chalmers Collective Bargaining and Finances, July 26, 1942; 7.
      - Smith to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 11, 1942; 8.
      - Smith to Matles Regarding Local 239 Allis Chalmers Strike, December 19, 1946; 9.
      - Edward Ventola to UE Regarding International Harvester Strike, November 3, 1952; 10.
      - Ventola to Emspak Regarding International Harvester Strike, November 22, 1952; 11.
      - Ventola to Emspak Regarding Address Change, May 27, 1954; 12.
      - Charles Wojchowski to Matles Regarding Local 239 Annual Banquet, December 21, 1955; 13.
      - Edward Wysocki to UE Regarding Finances, February 17, 1946; 14.
      - Wysocki to UE Regarding Political Action Committee, November 3, 1947; 15.
    - Local 239 Washington Allis-Chalmers Conference, February 14-18, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 106)
      - John Alberto to James Matles, February 14, 1941; 1.
      - Matles to Local 239, February 18, 1941; 2.
    - Local 239 Strike, May 21-26, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 107)
      - Carl Carlson Telegram to James Matles, May 21, 1941; 1.
      - Matles' Secretary to Carlson, May 26, 1941; 2.
    - Local 239 War Labor Board Case, June 24-December 28, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 108)
      - Local 239 Telegram to James Matles, June 24, 1942; 1.
      - Neil Brant to Matles, December 28, 1942; 2.
    - Local 239 Financial Problems, January 23-April 29, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 109)
      - Richard Linsley to Julius Emspak, January 23, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Linsley, February 25-April 29, 1943; 2-3.
      - Unsigned Memo to Emspak, 4.
    - Local 239 Per Capita Payments, January 21-February 11, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 110)
      - Joseph Smith to Julius Emspak, January 21, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Jack Simon, February 1, 1946; 2.
      - Simon to Emspak, February 11, 1946; 3.
    - Local 239 Strike, May 1-December 4, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 111)
      - Donald Tormey to James Matles, May 1, 1946; 1.
      - Jim Marino to Emspak, July 16-October 5, 1946; 2-3.
      - Issues in Dispute at Boston Allis-Chalmers, October 21, 1946; 4.
      - Matles Telegram to Joseph Smith, December 4, 1946; 5.
    - Local 239 LaPorte Allis-Chalmers Conference, April 1-8, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 112)
      - James Matles to Joseph Geraneo, April 1, 1953; 1.
      - William Murdock Telegram to Matles, April 2, 1953; 2.
      - Matles to Geraneo, April 8, 1953; 3.
    - Local 239 Boston Automatic Radio, May 26, 1937-February 23, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Local 239 Correspondence, December 1940-July 1954 (Box 10, Folder 114)
      - James Matles to Jack Schubert Regarding United Auto Workers and Local 239 Officers, December 27, 1940; 1.
      - Roger Fosdick to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 239 Officers, March 26, 1941; 2.
      - Carl Carlson Telegram to Matles Regarding Allis Chalmers Conference and Finances, December 2, 1941; 3.
      - Carlson Telegram to Matles Regarding Allis Chalmers Collective Bargaining, 1946; 4.
      - Joseph Smith Telegram to Matles Regarding Allis Chalmers Conference, January 18, 1949; 5.
      - Smith Telegram to Local 765 Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 22, 1950; 6.
      - Local 239 Annual Banquet with Two Tickets, January 23, 1954; 7.
      - Charles Wojchowski to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Joseph McCarthy Hearings, July 1954; 8.
  - Local 240
    - Local 240 Officers Lists, May 1947-February 1950 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Local 240 Incoming Correspondence, January 30, 1943-May 27, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 116)
      - Julius Emspak to Gordon Juliano Regarding Veterans and Finances, December 3, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Olga Bruchausky Regarding Dues, January 30, 1943-January 17, 1947; 2-3.
      - Emspak to Dorothy Winand Regarding Address Change, May 22, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to Etta Porgamon Regarding Bridgeport UE News, May 27, 1949; 5.
    - Local 240 Outgoing Correspondence, November 1946-June 1948 (Box 10, Folder 117)
      - Irving Balbirer to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Dues and Organization, February 17, 1947; 1.
      - Peter Stritch to Alexander Wiley Regarding Political Action and Mundt Bill, June 1948; 2.
      - Dorothy Winard to UE Regarding Dues, November 7, 1946; 3.
    - Local 240 Organization, March 28-April 16, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 118)
      - Hugh Harley to Joseph Dermody, March 28, 1945; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Harley, March 29, 1945; 2.
      - Thomas Fitzpatrick to Dermody, April 9, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Fitzpatrick, April 10, 1945; 4.
      - Fitzpatrick to Emspak, April 11, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Fitzpatrick, April 12, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Harley, April 16, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to Paul Seymour, April 16, 1945; 8.
    - Local 240 Dues, November 11, 1946-February 19,1947 (Box 10, Folder 119)
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Caiazza, November 11, 1946; 1.
      - Emspak to Paul Seymour with February 17, 1947, Irving Balbirer Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, February 19, 1947; 2.
  - Local 241
    - Local 241 Officers Lists, July 1946 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Local 241 Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Edmund Izzo, July 18, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Local 241 Outgoing Correspondence, Edmund Izzo to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 241 Hytron Collective Bargaining, July 12, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Local 241 Finances, 1945-1947 (Box 10, Folder 123)
      - Charter Supplies, April 15, 1945; 1.
      - Ledger, 1946-1947; 2.
    - Local 241 Organization, April 15-16, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 124)
      - Julius Emspak to Donald Bollen, April 15, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Paul Seymour, April 16, 1945; 2.
    - Local 241 Hartford M.H. Rhodes Incorporation, June 12-November 22, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Local 241 Strike, September 20-October 21, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 126)
      - Donald Tormey to James Matles, September 20, 1946; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Tormey, September 26, 1946; 2.
      - Tormey to James Matles, September 30, 1946; 3.
      - Nat Shelman to Emspak, October 1-13, 1946; 4-5.
      - David Ratner to Shelman, October 21, 1946; 6.
    - Local 241 Disbanding, March 4-April 2, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 127)
      - Paul Seymour to Julius Emspak, March 4, 1947; 1.
      - Nat Shelman to Emspak, April 2, 1947; 2.
    - Local 241 Correspondence, Nat Shelman to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues, Supplies and Local 241 Officers, July 31, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Local 242
    - Local 242 Officers Lists, August 25, 1943-April 30, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Local 242 Incoming Correspondence, June 26, 1939-November 12, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 130)
      - Julius Emspak to Local 242 Regarding Supplies, June 26, 1939; 1.
      - Emspak to J. Alfred Evans Regarding Supplies, August 28, 1939; 2.
      - Emspak to Evans Regarding Mailing List, October 14, 1940; 3.
      - Emspak to Joseph Minder Regarding Dues and Women, February 26, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Walter Fuchs Regarding Local 242 Officers, July 16, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak to Fuchs Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, August 26, 1941; 6.
      - Emspak to Fuchs Regarding Time-study, Labor Law and Grievances, September 17, 1941; 7.
      - Emspak to Fuchs Regarding Unemployment, October 1, 1941; 8.
      - Emspak to Walter Zyuski Regarding Veterans and Finances, November 12, 1945; 9.
    - Local 242 Outgoing Correspondence, August 16, 1939-November 6, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 131)
      - Edith Balcomino to UE Regarding Local 242 Officers, October 13, 1942; 1.
      - J. Alfred Evans to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, August 16, 1939; 2.
      - Walter Fuchs to UE Regarding Local 242 Officers, July 11, 1941; 3.
      - Fuchs to Emspak Regarding Local 242 Blake Manufacturing Contracts and Local 242 Officers, July 18, 1941; 4.
      - Fuchs to Emspak Regarding Wages and Ever-ready Flashlight, August 1, 1941; 5.
      - Fuchs to James Matles Regarding American Federation of Labor, August 21, 1941; 6.
      - Fuchs to Emspak Regarding Time-study, Grievances and Labor Law, August 19, 1941; 7.
      - Fuchs to Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment, September 25, 1941; 8.
      - Fuchs to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Political Action, October 8, 1941; 9.
      - Walter Juszywski to UE Regarding Finances, July 6, 1945; 10.
      - Juszywski to UE Regarding Veterans and Finances, November 6, 1945; 11.
      - Joseph Minder to Emspak Regarding Women, Hours and Dues, Februray 18, 1941; 12.
      - Minder to Matles Regarding Local 242 Clinton Manufacturing Collective Bargaining, March 24, 1941; 13.
      - Maurice Sachse to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Military Conversion, May 4, 1942; 14.
    - Local 242 Salary and Expense Letters, December 26, 1940-December 5, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 132)
      - A. Evans, December 26, 1940-September 9, 1941; 1-2.
      - Maurice Sachse, December 5, 1941; 2.
    - Local 242 Financial Ledger, 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Local 242 Retirement Plan, April 1-18, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 134)
      - Blake Manufacturing Cooperative Retirement Income Plan with April 8, 1941, Joseph Minder Letter to Julius Emspak, April 1, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Minder, April 18, 1941; 2.
    - Local 242 Contracts, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 135)
      - Walter Fuchs to Julius Emspak, January 31, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Fuchs, February 18, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Richard Linsley, February 18, 1942; 3.
      - Contract, 1941-1942; 4.
    - Local 242 Springfield Blake Manufacturing, July 2, 1937-February 5, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - Local 242 Memo Regarding Local 242 Secession, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - Local 242 Leaflets, September-October 1941 (Box 10, Folder 138)
      - "Committee to Keep Clinton at Work", September 17, 1941; 1.
      - "Keep Clinton at Work Defending Democracy", October 1941; 2.
  - Local 243
    - Local 243 Officers Lists, April, 1942-November 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Local 243 Incoming Correspondence, June 27, 1942-November 9, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Julius Emspak to Vincent Romeo Regarding Local 243 Picnic, June 27, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Lillian Weissman Regarding Staff Finances, April 30, 1943; 2.
      - Eleanor Holden to Weissman Regarding Address Change, May 7, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Esther Lillo Regarding Veterans and Finances, June 1, 1945; 4.
      - Emspak to Nicholas Fortino Regarding Veterans and Finances, July 2, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Madeline Scillia Regarding Local 243 Strike, July 13, 1948; 6.
      - Emspak to Fortino Regarding Finances, December 6, 1949; 7.
      - Emspak to Fortino Regarding Shop Stewards Banquet, February 19-21, 1951; 8-9.
      - Emspak to Fortino Regarding Local 243 Banquet with Ticket, October 9, 1953; 10.
      - Emspak to Fortino Regarding Finances, November 9, 1953; 11.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Harold Peters Regarding Political Action Committee, April 25, 1944; 12.
      - Fitzgerald to Albert Pacileo Regarding Local 242 Sargent Strikes, April 17, 1947; 13.
      - Fitzgerald to Fortino Regarding Membership Meeting, May 21, 1951; 14.
      - James Matles to Michael Mendygral Regarding Membership Meeting, April 21, 1942; 15.
      - Matles to Mendygral, November 23, 1942; 16.
      - Matles to Fortino, November 5, 1947; 17.
      - Matles' Secretary to Fortino Regarding Stewards Banquet, February 20, 1951; 18.
    - Local 243 Outgoing Correspondence, December 17, 1943-October 28, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Nancy Cirillo to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, December 28, 1945; 1.
      - Nicholas Fortino to Julius Emspak, December 17, 1943; 2.
      - Fortino to Tom Wright Regarding Local 243 Officers, March 16, 1944; 3.
      - Fortino to General Executive Board Regarding Veterans and Finances, June 29, 1945; 4.
      - Fortino to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, May 22-December 2, 1946; 5-7.
      - Fortino to James Matles, October 19, 1947; 8.
      - Fortino to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 20-December 12, 1947; 9-10.
      - Fortino to Emspak Regarding Local 243 Sargent Contracts, July 15, 1948; 11.
      - Fortino to UE Regarding Finances, December 2, 1949; 12.
      - Fortino to Matles Regarding Stewards Banquet, February 16, 1951; 13.
      - Fortino to Emspak Regarding Stewards Banquet, February 16, 1951; 14.
      - Fortino to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting and Wages, May 17, 1951; 15.
      - Fortino to Emspak Regarding International Harvester Strike, October 31-December 1, 1952; 16-19.
      - Fortino to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 243 Sargent Strike, July 8, 1955; 20.
      - Fortino to Emspak Regarding Supplies, October 28, 1953; 21.
      - Esther Lillo to UE Regarding Supplies, May 26, 1945; 22.
      - Lillo to Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 15, 1951; 23.
      - Lillo to Fitzgerald Regarding Publicity, March 29, 1951; 24.
    - Local 243 Outgoing Correspondence, April 14, 1942-May 2, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Michael Mendygral to James Matles Regarding Local 243 Officers, April 14, 1942; 1.
      - Mendygral to Matles Regarding Overtime and War Labor Board, November 17, 1942; 2.
      - Laura Montefusco to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 243 Officers, January 18, 1943; 3.
      - Albert Pacileo to Matles Regarding Racism, Civil Rights Committee and Factionalism with Pacileo Letter to Philip Murray, January 17, 1947; 4.
      - Pacileo to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 243 Sargent Collective Bargaining, April 14, 1947; 5.
      - Pacileo Telegram Regarding Local 243 Sargent Strike, May 2, 1947; 6.
      - Harold Peters to Fitzgerald Regarding Black Workers and Political Action, April 18, 1944; 7.
      - Vincent Romeo to Emspak Regarding Local 243 Picnic with Tickets, June 23, 1942; 8.
      - Romeo to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 243 Picnic, June 23, 1942; 9.
      - Lilliam Weissman to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, April 27, 1943; 10.
      - Weissman to UE Regarding Mailing Address, May 6, 1943; 11.
      - Weissman to Eleanor Holden Regarding Conneticut Malleable Castings Organization, May 12, 1943; 12.
      - Weissman to UE Regarding Local 243 Officers, May 21, 1943; 13.
    - Local 243 New Haven Correspondence, January 11, 1957-February 25, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Local 243 Receipts, February 3-24, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Local 243 Chartering, April 3-August 19, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Charles Rivers Memo, April 3, 1941; 1.
      - Rivers to Julius Emspak, April 3, 1941; 2.
      - Rivers to Stella, July 21, 1941; 3.
      - J.E. Lawless to Emspak, August 19, 1941; 4.
    - Local 243 Strike Mediation, November 8-10, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - James Matles Telegram to John Steelman, November 8, 1941; 1.
      - Steelman Telegram to Matles, November 10, 1941; 2.
    - Local 243 Amalgamation, July-October 1944 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Joseph Caiazza to Julius Emspak, July 1944; 1.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Caiazza, July 18, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Caiazza, October 16, 1944; 3.
      - Caiazza to Emspak, October 17, 1944; 4.
    - Local 243 Separate Charters, May 5-June 11, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Paul Seymour Memo to Albert Fitzgerald, May 5, 1954; 1.
      - Janet Barish to Donald Tormey, May 26, 1954; 2.
      - Tormey to Julius Emspak with Letter to Emspak, May 27, 1954; 3.
      - Seymour Memo to Emspak, June 1, 1954; 4.
      - Seymour Memo, June 2, 1954; 5.
      - Seymour Memo to Emspak with June 2, 1954, Local 243 Board Meeting Notes and June 2, 1954, Wiliam Zimmerman Letter to Emspak, June 22, 2954; 6.
    - Local 243 New Haven Sargent Manufacturing, June 24-December 10, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Local 243 New Haven Sargent Lock Company, December 7, 1981-August 15, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Local 243 Legislative Committee and Political Action, April 24, 1971-March 7, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Local 243 Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, April 17, 1970-September 15, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Local 243 Corresponcence, Proposal and Ticket, December 16, 1941-October 24, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - F.A. Smith to Fellow Employees Regarding Sargent National Labor Relations Board Elections, December 16, 1941; 1.
      - Proposals Concerning Employment Relations to Which Sargent is Willing to Agree, February 1942; 2.
      - Michael Kozar to James Matles Regarding Finances with March 2, 1942, Bonding Form, February 25, 1942; 3.
      - Peter Boryszewski to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 11, 1942; 4.
      - Matles to All Locals Regarding Overtime and Executive Order 9240, September 30, 1942; 5.
      - Martin Hovriham to Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism, March 8, 1943; 6.
      - David Scribner Memo to Emspak Regarding Local 243 Sargent Strike, April 11, 1947; 7.
      - Lillian Rosenberg to Albert Smith Regarding Local 243 Mettler Brothers Strike, May 29, 1951; 8.
      - Emma Memo to Kay Regarding Local 243 Sargent Strike and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, September 24, 1951; 9.
      - Local 243 Stewards Banquet Ticket, October 24, 1953; 10.
    - Local 243 Leaflets, December 1941-February 1951 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - "Sargent and Company Gos UE-CIO", December 1941; 1.
      - Albert Pacileo to Members Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry and Safety Car, April 2, 1948; 2.
      - "It Is No Secret" Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry and Safety Car, 1948; 3.
      - Banquent Committee to Members Regarding Local 243 Officers Banquet, February 1951; 4.
      - "Union Meeting Tuesday", 5.
      - "Facts You Should Know" Regarding Organization, 6.
      - "Vote Yes" Regarding Organization, 7.
  - Local 244
    - Local 244 Officers Lists, April 5, 1948-July 25, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Local 244 Incoming Correspondence, October 17, 1945-January 30, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 18)